topnewspress.com 2016-12-16

# Privacy Policy-Affiliate Disclosure - Top new stories, latest breaking news from around the world | Top new stories, latest breaking news from around the world

**Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we give this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third-party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](view-source:http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, TopNewsPress.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third-party advertisers.

**Other Cookies**  
We may use some external services ([google.com/analytics](http://google.com/analytics) and/or [quantcast.com](http://quantcast.com/)) to know about the web traffic. You may visit google.com/analytics and quantcast.com to review their privacy policies. You may also visit <http://networkadvertising.org/choices> to opt-out all the other advertisement cookies on the internet. 

<http://www.maxbounty.com/privacy.cfm>  
<http://www.infolinks.com/infolinks-privacy-policy>

**Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting TopNewsPress.com, the IP address used to get access to the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third-party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**AFFILIATE DISCLOSURE:**

The owner of this site is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com, amazonsupply.com, or myhabit.com

Some outgoing text links to third party sites might generate commission revenue/compensation to this site if you make a purchase at those third party sites after clicking any link on this site (topnewspress.com). The content of this site is not affected from advertisements to promote them better and to generate more commission/advertisement revenue. Also please do your own research before buying something on the internet.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions about the privacy policy of [TopNewsPress.com](http://132.148.68.80/~topnewspress/) then you may contact us at <http://132.148.68.80/~topnewspress/contact-us/>
